(Penny:)Nope.
(Leonard:)Let me see.
(Leonard:)Yeah, there.
(Leonard:)What number were
you putting in?
(Raj:)Uh...
(Leonard:)You don't know my
birthday, do you?
(Penny:)Yes, I do.
Well, what is it?
(Amy:)May.
(Leonard:)May what?
(Penny:)I'm not gonna say
your password out loud.
(Penny:)That is not secure.
(Leonard:)You don't know your own
husband's birthday.
(Sheldon:)Well...
(Penny:)you don't know everything
about me.
(Leonard:)Your birthday is December 2,
(Leonard:)you grew up on
Perkins Street,
(Leonard:)the last four digits
of your social are
7-6-2-1,
(Leonard:)and the odds of me letting
you forget this are zero.
(Penny:)Oh, look at us.
(Penny:)Our last Thanksgiving
as husband and wife.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Raj:)Hi.